<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<ClassDocs>
	<ClassMembers name="DataStorage">
		<summary>
			Class responsible for storing and managing loaded image data in a thread-safe manner.
			It maintains an internal dictionary of ImageDataContainer objects, indexed by file path,
			and provides controlled access for adding, retrieving, clearing, and listing stored images.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="ToolProcessor">
		<summary>
			Class responsible for running enabled image-processing tools on all stored images.
			It retrieves images from the DataStorage and applies each active ToolBase instance
			from the ToolsManager in a parallelized manner to improve performance.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="ImageDataContainer">
		<summary>
			Class representing image data loaded from the file system.
			It stores the source file path and optionally the raw byte content of the image.
			Used as the primary data container for image processing operations.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="ImageLoader">
		<summary>
			Static class responsible for asynchronously loading image files from disk and storing
			them into a <see cref="DataStorage"/> instance.
			It reads raw image bytes and wraps them into <see cref="ImageDataContainer"/> objects, making them available for later processing.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="ToolBase">
		<summary>
			Abstract base class for all image-processing tools.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="ToolsManager">
		<summary>
			Class responsible for managing all image-processing tools in the system.
			Provides functionality to register new tools and access the collection of registered tools.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="WatermarkTool">
		<summary>
			Tool that applies a watermark image onto target images.
			Supports configurable watermark image path, opacity, and position.
			Inherits from <see cref="ToolBase"/>.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="ScaleTool">
		<summary>
			Tool that proportionally scales an image based on a scale factor.
			The scale factor can range from 0 to 2.
			Inherits from <see cref="ToolBase"/>.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="ResizeTool">
		<summary>
			Tool that resizes an image to specific width and height values.
			Width and height must be greater than zero and within reasonable bounds.
			Inherits from <see cref="ToolBase"/>.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="FlipTool">
		<summary>
			Tool that flips an image horizontally, vertically, or both.
			Inherits from <see cref="ToolBase"/>.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="BrightnessTool">
		<summary>
			Tool that adjusts the brightness of an image.
			Brightness multiplier must be greater than 0 and less than or equal to 3.
			Inherits from <see cref="ToolBase"/>.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="TabContext">
		<summary>
			Represents the context of a tab in the application, managing both image storage and associated image-processing tools.
			Provides methods to execute tools and validate their states.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="ActionPanel">
		<summary>
			UserControl that provides actions for importing, processing, and exporting images.
			Connects with <see cref="PreviewPanel"/> and <see cref="TabContext"/> to manage images and tools.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="PreviewPanel">
		<summary>
			UserControl that displays a list of imported images and shows a preview of the selected image.
			Integrates with <see cref="TabContext"/> to apply tools and retrieve images.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="ToolsPanel">
		<summary>
			UserControl that manages tool settings and interactions for the current tab.
			Connects with <see cref="TabContext"/> and <see cref="PreviewPanel"/> to enable/disable tools
			and update previews in real-time.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="MainWindow">
		<summary>
			The main window of the LIMS application.
			Manages the initialization and wiring of all panels, including <see cref="ActionPanel"/>,
			<see cref="ToolsPanel"/>, and <see cref="PreviewPanel"/>.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="HeaderPanel">
		<summary>
			UserControl that represents the header section of the LIMS application interface.
			Provides buttons for accessing preferences and zoom controls.
			Handles opening of the preferences menu and placeholder methods for zooming in and out.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

	<ClassMembers name="Logger">
		<summary>
			Static class used for thread-safe logging.
			Writes timestamped log entries into per-day log files under the application Log directory.
		</summary>
	</ClassMembers>

</ClassDocs>
